[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Crabtree!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Sherman"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Rachel, before we get to your interview, which is a great coo for you and for CNN and what was your reaction when you are watching it live to what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, actually we hear things like that all of the time so I was a bit surprised at the reaction that mushroomed out from what Richard Sherman said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "PERSON": ["Rachel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What do you not regret about all of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, there isn't much about that I regret.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "is that the background of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "That's the short version of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Is that the clean version?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "That's the -- and we're going to keep it clean.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Did it get nastier than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I'm going to keep it clean.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How do you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "You have to have that switch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Crabtree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Do you have a problem with depression?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Not often really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Compton"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Did you fight a lot as a kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Not everybody in Compton is a gang member.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Richard, have you gone downhill since college?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Do you feel you're untouchable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "I'm not afraid of anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "And that's what it's about, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "ICHOLS: Well, it's interesting you showed that advertisement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Did you understand what he was doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, you know, it's really interesting because people are quick to judge and they don't know the back story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Just to clarify, Carl, you know, Chris Christie personally said to you if you run, we're going to come after you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Oh, absolutely he said that on the telephone call.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carl", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "What is your reaction to that denial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, that isn't really surprising.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Guadagno"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Just as an overview, Carl, before I move to the others, do you think Chris Christie therefore is a bully as many are trying to portray him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, you know, I actually I want to kind of get to what their comment was because the reality is that I was approved by judges and also the law judge, the Guadagno is the one who actually pulled me off the ballot twice.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carl", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "You were as an athlete so I don't know why you didn't expect in the political route?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "How do you see this playing out in the bigger picture for Chris Christie because a lot of concerns at the moment are refusing to put their heads over the parapet for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, look.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Ever met one of your victims?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "I have not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No one just sought me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Why haven't you sought them out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "You know, I don't want to intrude anybody's life and, you know ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "And not just to that but to the interview as a whole?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I thought the interview was fascinating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Am I madly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think you're mad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Ben Ferguson, did you like the Wolf of Wall Street?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Why should it be different rules for a trader given that it seems to me like he was certainly pretty sincere with the remorse he showed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Well I think that the difference in a lot of ways is the way you affect other people's lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernie Madoff"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Leigh, (inaudible) to get in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "No one is saying this about Bernie Madoff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "He was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Because I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 399, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "... I mean it's been so much terror activity ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Is it beards staying in the Sochi games?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "No, she's shaving it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sochi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 453, "question": "IEIRA: Why do you even encourage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I think he's very ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Don't you think he looks good in that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I'm not convinced by the beard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Pretty extraordinary in the modern age, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Is that accurate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "We have a lot of crazy laws in our country, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "We already have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I watch CNN.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Richard, are you aware of your wife's key knowledge of the night life in Sochi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "More than you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sochi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Does that hurt (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "It was bloody painful if I'm honest with you, Richard, is it as painful as it looks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How do you deal with that on an emotional level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, I think you just accept it, you know, what is, what it is and I've never stopped fighting it and this stem cell trial is really a break with traditional therapies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What frustrations are there for both of you about this ongoing relentlessly tedious process which is what it must be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Well, that's part of the frustration that it is ongoing and tedious and you don't know from one day to the next what you're going to get and there are exacerbations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "So those who have opposed stem cell research, what do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I'll say they're wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "You don't want to create other Richards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", ":", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "How did you eventually make that break?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "I -- the pain in what I believe was heaven, got to the point that I was willing to down (ph) myself to hell to escape it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ":", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "ORGAN: In terms of the detail of your suffering, how bad was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "My dad was sexually abusing me starting at about eight years old continuing on up into my teenage years -- begged for help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffs"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "How does that stigma make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "The stigma of having a last name Jeffs -- it's kind of a double edged sword.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "To actually have lived through it, how bad was it for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "It was completely horrible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "When you talked together -- obviously, you worked together on this show \"Escaping the Prophet,\" do you feel a bond with other people that have been through this that nobody else can really understand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "That's exactly the way you put it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Flora, you both believed that the power of Warren Jeffs continues even from inside prison, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Jeffs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "In what way does it manifest itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Warren is still doing church services from his prison cell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "... inside prison?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "And was that part of the technique, Brandon, to keep everybody under control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "It was the scare tactic.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brandon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "And the parallel is that you were just saying in the break there quite chillingly that part of being part of Jeffs' sect is that you're encouraged to believe that one day you will go and kill to achieve the second coming, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "ESSOP: We are to become God's army.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Jeffs"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Brandon, how many people are out there who are still disciples of Warren Jeffs, what he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Disciples of Warren Jeffs, I'd say there still about 10,000 plus.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Jeffs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "And how many of those from your knowledge, from your instinct, would if it they came to it be capable of killing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "They would obey him blindly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "You think he still wheels the same power even though he's imprisoned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "I definitely still feel he wheels the exact same power because his word is god.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Jeffs"]}, "docId": "140121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 713, "question": "Flora, you got out, Brandon you got out, and to anyone who may be watching this who is part of this sect and completely brain washed even to the point of being murderous potentially, what do you say to them to trigger a different thought process that may make the break and escape?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "CC", "TO", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 714, "answer": "You know, I want them to realize that their brain was not given to Warren Jeffs.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brandon"]}}]